Kitana Meuandane

Woodbridge, VA | (703) 798-0172 | <u>Kitanabdane@gmail.com</u> | <u>linkedin.com/in/kitanameuandane</u> Portfolio: <u>kitanabdane.github.io/portfolio</u>

Career Objective:

Information Technology graduate with a background in creative web design and development, providing IT support, product innovation, and 7+ years of efficient customer service. Seeking a full-time position in web development and IT support with a work-driven and detail-oriented mindset. Committed to implementing my technical and interpersonal skills to make significant contributions to clients, organizations, and executives.

Education:

Bachelor of Science, Information Technology (2020-2023) George Mason University, Fairfax, VA **Associate of Science, Information Technology** (2017-2019) Northern Virginia Community College, Annandale, VA

Skills:

Microsoft Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Project, Teams, Outlook | HTML | CSS | Java | SQL | PHP VS Code | Square | Wordpress | Sharepoint | Dreamweaver | Figma | Photoshop | Tableau Creative | Multitasker | Collaborative | Detail-oriented | Organized | Communicator | Adaptable

Relevant Academic Projects:

IT Capstone Project: Admin and Client Dashboard for Tax Documents (Fall 2022-Spring 2023)

- Collaborated virtually and in-person with capstone team and client to improve their business by reducing costs, strengthen performance, and create efficient scheduling (Teams, MS Project)
- Extensive research on applications that could be cost efficient and beneficial for the business
- Developed a client and admin dashboard for easy use of document exchanges and accessibility
- Multiple testing, training, and maintenance sessions to ensure the application was secure, efficient, and useful before handing it off to the client for use
- API Integrations and various applications used for the development process (AWS, Figma, Visual Studio Code, Budibase, Dropbox Docsend)

IT Project Management (Fall 2021)

- Case study assigned to team where electronic documents were implemented into a hospital to take over paper records and documents, needing to identify business scope, problems, benefits, and impact on finances, leadership, employees, and clients
- Written project plan statements; team presentations showing visual forms of projects using Gantt charts, work breakdown structure, Pareto charts, etc.
- Constant use of SWOT analysis to identify problems and solutions, improving the business's growth
- Critical path method used to organize and complete deadlines, delivering a successful project outcome on time with thorough team contribution

Multimedia and Web Design Project: Mock Bakery Website (Spring 2021)

- Applications and tools used to create website were Dreamweaver, Photoshop, Animate, Bootstrap, Ajax, W3C Validation, and jQuery Validation
- Understood the detailed design plan of creating a user-friendly website that appeals to audience, creativity, accessibility, and technical issues
- Learned website design and appeal based on a company's objective and scope
- Ability to implement, test, publish, and maintain a website while ensuring responsive web design and appropriate guidelines

Experience:

Server/Lead Trainer/Social Media Champion/Catering Event Specialist, Chuy's Restaurant (Woodbridge, VA | 2016-Current)

- Adapted to various positions in a high-paced environment throughout my career term, lead trainer in serving, hosting, and to-go departments. Assisted in smaller management roles and duties
- **Social Media Champion**: Marketing skills used by creating and designing advertisements, using photo-editing software and creative captions, showcasing restaurant culture to help gain traffic
- Efficient and fast-paced customer service provided on a daily work basis, attracting guests and regulars by enhancing the restaurant experience; competitive in food and drink sales
- Able to multitask under pressure and in a collaborative environment, keeping the workspace consistently organized
- Lead trainer, ensuring consistency of efficient work displayed by all employees in the server department
- Assists in planning, delivering, and advertising to catering events, contributing to restaurant sales, increasing customer satisfaction, and word of mouth by networking

Sales Associate, The North Face Outlet (Woodbridge, VA | 2017-2018)

- Knowledge of product technology and specifications to assist customers, increasing store revenue
- Kept a positive and enthusiastic attitude throughout daily shifts toward customers and throughout the workplace
- Balanced cash handling, Organized and kept registers secure before, throughout, and at end of shifts
- Daily use of suggestive selling and consultative sales to understand customer needs and wants

Volunteer:

Culinary Teacher Assistant, Squarespace Mentor, Potomac Senior High School (Dumfries, VA | Current)

- Assists teacher in helping students improve their cooking and baking skills, preparing them for future culinary challenges
- Show students how to price food items, advertise and display their work, help them gain an understanding of the business and kitchen side of culinary, giving advice on what makes a business consistent and successful, and how to market themselves
- Presenting Squarespace as an option for business startups, teaching students how to use the application by building designs, pages, create a working checkout page, etc.